
export const quizQuestions_4 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'In React, which attribute is used to associate a label with a form element?',
      choices: ['label', 'for', 'id', 'name'],
      correctAnswer: 'htmlFor',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of controlled components in React forms?',
      choices: ['They are components with enhanced styles', 'They manage form state using React state', 'They handle form submission automatically', 'They provide built-in validation for forms'],
      correctAnswer: 'They manage form state using React state',
    },
    {
      question: 'In a controlled component, what React feature is used to handle input changes?',
      choices: ['onChange', 'onInput', 'onClick', 'onSubmit'],
      correctAnswer: 'onChange',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which React hook is commonly used for form validation?',
      choices: ['useEffect()', 'useReducer()', 'useForm()', 'useFormValidation()'],
      correctAnswer: 'useReducer()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the HTML `<form>` element in a React application?',
      choices: ['It defines a container for form elements', 'It creates a new page for the form', 'It handles form submissions automatically', 'It triggers a form validation event'],
      correctAnswer: 'It defines a container for form elements',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which HTML attribute is used for defining the type of an input element in a form?',
      choices: ['inputType', 'elementType', 'type', 'formType'],
      correctAnswer: 'type',
    },
    {
      question: 'In React, what is the purpose of the `value` attribute in an input element?',
      choices: ['To set the initial value of the input', 'To specify the maximum length of the input', 'To define the input type', 'To add placeholder text'],
      correctAnswer: 'To set the initial value of the input',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which method is commonly used in React to prevent the default behavior of a form submission?',
      choices: ['preventDefault()', 'stopPropagation()', 'haltEvent()', 'cancelEvent()'],
      correctAnswer: 'preventDefault()',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the role of the `useState` hook in handling form input?',
      choices: ['To define the form structure', 'To manage the form validation', 'To handle form submission', 'To manage the input value in React state'],
      correctAnswer: 'To manage the input value in React state',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the `required` attribute in an HTML form element?',
      choices: ['It specifies the maximum length of the input', 'It makes the input read-only', 'It prevents the form from being submitted', 'It indicates that the input must be filled out before submitting the form'],
      correctAnswer: 'It indicates that the input must be filled out before submitting the form',
    },
  ],
}